Francisco Martínez.

JS JAVASCRIPT PYTHON ME MARKDOWN O GHOST NOTEPAD++ W WORDPRESS NOTION

Technical Writer

Senior Technical Writer with over 23 years of experience and more than 16 years in writing and developing technical publications. Seeking work opportunities to further enhance my skills as a Technical Writer. 🚀 I'm also open to freelance writing and editing work.

✓ Accomplishments **Efficiency ▼** Goals

End result of docs

Contact

in LinkedIn GitHub Twitter

@ Send a mail

Experience

Tech Mahindra | TECHNICAL WRITER

Airbus L&M Programs Maintenance Docs TID Support

iuly 2017 - Present | Seville, Spain (Hybrid)

Quest Global | TECHNICAL WRITER

Airbus MRTT Catalog & Structure Manual Responsible

october 2006 - june 2017 | Seville, Spain

Abengoa | Senior Project Designer

october 2005 - october 2006 | Seville, Spain

Hidral | Senior Project Designer

ijune 2005 - october 2005 | Seville, Spain

Auxiple Outsourcing | Airbus A380 Technical Illustrator

苗 december 2004 - june 2005 | 🏶 Seville, Spain

Tecnocontrol | Senior Designer

september 2004 - december 2004 | \$\iiii \text{Seville, Spain}

Dinotec Industrial Draftsman

ijune 2004 - september 2004 | Seville, Spain

Nilo - Aqualia | Industrial Draftsman

october 2000 - june 2004 | Seville, Spain

Education

FPII Industrial Design (Certificate of Higher

Education)

Polytechnic Institute of Seville

iseptember 1998 - june 2001 | Seville, Spain

Languages

English: Full Professional Proficiency (B2)

Spanish: Fluent (Native)

Courses

IT Courses:

100% Responsive Web Design (HTML, CCS).

freeCodeCamp Certification.

70% Scientific Computing with Python. freeCodeCamp Certification.

50% JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures.

freeCodeCamp Certification.

100% Automation Engineer Certification: Maven-Jenkins-Selenium.TM Certificate.

100% Agile: Scrum Management. TM Certificate.

100% VBA and VBScript. TM Certificate.

TW and Design Courses:

100% Aircraft Systems Course: Electrical and Avionics.

100% Introduction to Aeronautical Systems: Hydraulic and Pneumatic.

100% CAD Specialist.

100% Mechanical Design with CATIA V5.

100% Office Business Management (MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint).

Languages Courses:

100% English Course Upper Intermediate (B2) Semi-Intensive.

100% English Course Intermediate (B1-B2).

100% English Pre-Intermediate level (A2).

100% Simplified Technical English (ASD-STE100 v4).

State of Skills

XML 90%	Markdown 80%	Wrinting 90%
HTML 80%	Arbortex 90%	Translation 70%
CSS 70%	Static Sites 70%	Al tools 60%
Javascript 45%	Wordpress 75%	SEO 60%

Main Interests

Reading: Enjoy reading fiction and non-fiction books on a wide range of topics, including science fiction, history, and technology.

Sports: Regularly participate in hiking and cycling to maintain physical fitness and mental well-being.

Travel: Passionate about exploring different cultures and have traveled to various countries to experience diverse lifestyles and broaden my horizons.

Volunteer Work: Actively involved in non-profit organizations.